RG 009, Office of the Attorney General
Connecticut State Library
- Series 2. Case Files, bulk
  - 1984-094, cubic feet
    - Merritt Parkway Files
      - Nellie M. Joyce - Greenwich, 1932-1934; Parcel number 9M. (Box 33)
      - Joseph and June Platt - Greenwich, 1932; Parcel number 11M. (Box 33)
      - William Goff - Greenwich, 1932; Parcel number 12M. (Box 33)
      - Carrie B. Sherwood - Greenwich, 1932-1933; Parcel number 14M. (Box 33)
      - Georgianna E. Lewis - Greenwich, 1932; Parcel number 19. (Box 33)
      - Alfred L. and Sarah Bernheim - Greenwich, 1932-1933; Parcel number 20M. (Box 33)
      - Edwin H. Schiffer - Greenwich, 1932-1933; Parcel number 22M. (Box 33)
      - T. Scudder, E.N. and E. Lockwood, and Catherine G. Marshall - Greenwich, 1932-1934; Parcel number 23M. (Box 33)
      - Catherine G. Marshall - Greenwich, 1932-1937; Parcel number 27M. (Box 33)
      - Helen Hodge - Greenwich, 1932-1933; Parcel number 28M. (Box 33)
      - Mary G. and Norman P. Ream - Greenwich, 1933; Parcel number 29. (Box 33)
      - Etta B.M. and Carrie E. Ferris - Greenwich, 1932; Parcel number 32M. (Box 33)
      - Florence C. Allaben - Greenwich, 1932-1933; Parcel number 33. (Box 33)
      - Robert T. Stone - Greenwich, 1932; Parcel number 34M. (Box 33)
      - Estate of John Sullivan - Greenwich, 1932-1935; Parcel number 34M. (Box 33)
      - Eugene F. Byrnes - Greenwich, 1932; Parcel number 34.5M. (Box 33)
      - George L. and Emma R. Ohrstrom - Greenwich, 1932-1934; Parcel number 35M. (Box 33)
      - The Beaver Dam Company - Greenwich, 1935-1936; Parcel number 35.5. (Box 33)
      - M. Roy and Almira R. Jackson - Greenwich, 1933; Parcel number 40M. (Box 33)
      - Joseph W. Cone and William S. Hirschberg - Greenwich, 1932-1934; Parcel number 41M. (Box 33)
      - Greenwich Water Company, 1933-1940; Parcel number 43M. (Box 33)
      - Joseph A. Lockhart - Greenwich, 1932; Parcel number 44.5M. (Box 33)
      - Quentin Twachtman - Greenwich, 1932; Parcel number 45.5M. (Box 33)
      - Glenville Power and Water Co. - Greenwich, 1933-1934 (Box 33)
      - Estate of Joseph Howland Hunt - Greenwich, 1932-1933; Parcel number 49.5M. (Box 33)
      - Summerfield Methodist Episcopal Church - Greenwich, 1932 (Box 33)
      - The Village Investment Co. - Greenwich, 1932 (Box 33)
      - Signora and Ivar Numme - Greenwich, 1931-1932 (Box 33)
      - Alvin Untermyer - Greenwich, 1932-1934 (Box 33)
      - Estate of John Sullivan - Greenwich, 1935; Parcel number 46-M B. (Box 33)
      - Estate of Georgia T. Fry - Greenwich, 1932-1936; Parcel number 49M. (Box 33)
      - Yandell, et al. - Greenwich, 1936; Parcel numbers 60-M-B and 62.5-M-C-D. (Box 33)
      - Mary E. Minor - Stamford, 1934; Parcel number 1. (Box 33)
      - Estate of Augustus June - Stamford, 1933-1936; 3 folders; Parcel numbers 2, 2C-2E. (Box 33)
      - Estate of George E. Farrington - Stamford, 1933-1934; Parcel number 3. (Box 33)
      - Lucia E. Farrington - Stamford, 1936; Parcel number 3.5. (Box 33)
      - Estate of H. O. Havemeyer - Stamford, 1936; Parcel number 4. (Box 33)
      - Fannie B. Goulden - Stamford, 1933-1934; Parcel number 5. (Box 33)
      - J. Wilfred Barrett - Stamford, 1936; Parcel number 5.5. (Box 33)
      - Wallace W. Delavan - Stamford, 1933; Parcel number 6. (Box 33)
      - Maurice Hertz - Stamford, 1933; Parcel number 7.5. (Box 33)
      - Martha V. Hertz - Stamford, 1935; Parcel number 7.5. (Box 33)
      - Katherine Wohlpart - Stamford, 1933; Parcel number 8. (Box 33)
      - Austin S. Haviland - Stamford, 1933; Parcel number 9. (Box 33)
      - William Haug - Stamford, 1933; Parcel number 10. (Box 33)
      - Estate of John Ryle - Stamford, 1934; Parcel number 11. (Box 33)
      - Adrien B. Tucker - Stamford, 1933; Parcel number 12. (Box 33)
      - Joseph S. Corbyn and Frederick G.B. Hoth - Stamford, 1933-1936; 2 folders; Parcel numbers 13 and 13B. (Box 33)
      - Emma Corbyn - Stamford, 1936; Parcel number 13.5. (Box 33)
      - Emma K. Hoth - Stamford, 1933; Parcel number 14. (Box 33)
      - C. Louise Clark - Stamford, 1933; Parcel number 15. (Box 33)
      - John H. Romme - Stamford, 1937; Parcel number 16. (Box 33)
      - B.T. Harris Corporation - Stamford, 1933-1936; 2 folders; Parcel numbers 17 and 17B. (Box 33)
      - Clara L. Merrill - Stamford, 1933; Parcel number 18. (Box 33)
      - Roberta Hart - Stamford, 1933-1934; Parcel number 19. (Box 33)
      - Marcella E. and Harry J. Quirke - Stamford, 1933; Parcel number 20. (Box 33)
      - Mary M. Borglum - Stamford, 1933-1934; Parcel number 21. (Box 33)
      - Edward B. Finch, James Donnelly, and Richard Dietzmann - Stamford, 1934; Parcel number 21.5. (Box 33)
      - Mary M. Borglum - Stamford, 1936; Parcel number 21-E. (Box 33)
      - Catherine Dunn - Stamford, 1935; Parcel number 22. (Box 33)
      - Hugh D. Catty - Stamford, 1936; Parcel number 23. (Box 33)
      - Thaddeus Hyatt and E. F. Hyatt - Stamford, 1934; Parcel number 24. (Box 33)
      - Catherine Dunn - Stamford, 1936; Parcel numbers 22C and 22D. (Box 33)
      - Joseph E. Gilbert - Stamford, 1936-1940; Parcel number 24.5. (Box 33)
      - Lillian C. Edmonds - Stamford, 1933-1936; 2 folders; Parcel numbers 25 and 25B. (Box 33)
      - Lizzie R. Hatch - Stamford, 1933; Parcel number 26. (Box 33)
      - Sagamore Holding Co. - Stamford, 1933; Parcel number 27. (Box 33)
      - Clarence P. and Belle W. Hanly - Stamford, 1933; Parcel number 28. (Box 33)
      - Samuel Hunter Richey - Stamford, 1933; Parcel number 29. (Box 33)
      - Marguerite L. Reid - Stamford, 1933; Parcel number 30. (Box 33)
      - Blue Ribbon Farms, Inc. - Westport, 1936-1937; 2 folders; Parcel numbers 20 and 20B. (Box 33)
      - Connecticut Light and Power Company - Norwalk, 1936-1937; Parcel number 21.5. (Box 33)
      - Estate of John S. Wakeman - Westport, 1936; Parcel number 21. (Box 33)
      - Lucie D. Woolson - Westport, 1936; Parcel number 22. (Box 33)
      - John Puzzak - Westport, 1936; Parcel number 23. (Box 33)
      - Euclid Couture - Westport, 1936; Parcel number 24. (Box 33)
      - Mary M. Reynolds - Westport, 1936; Parcel number 25. (Box 33)
      - Robert R. Mills - Westport, 1936; Parcel number 26. (Box 33)
      - Mary M. Inman - Westport, 1936; Parcel number 27. (Box 33)
      - Miscellaneous, circa 1933-1941, undated (Box 33)
        Folder contains an incomplete investigative report and schedules of diverted labor, equipment, and materials.
      - Herman Aaron - Norwalk, 1936; Parcel numbers 30C-30D. (Box 34)
      - Knorr - Norwalk, 1936; Parcel number 31. (Box 34)
      - Ella Louise Disbrow - Norwalk, 1936-1937; Parcel number 32. (Box 34)
      - Sigefridus G. Van Rygersma - Norwalk, 1934-1935; Parcel number 33. (Box 34)
      - Harriett A. Breese - Norwalk, 1937; Parcel number 34. (Box 34)
      - William T. Gregory - Norwalk, 1936; Parcel number 35. (Box 34)
      - George E. Simmons - Norwalk, 1937; Parcel number 36. (Box 34)
      - All Company, Inc. - Norwalk, 1934; Parcel number 37. (Box 34)
      - Clover Manufacturing Co. - Norwalk, 1936-1937; Parcel number 38. (Box 34)
      - Elbert H. Raymond - Norwalk, 1936; Parcel number 39. (Box 34)
      - Mildred W. Blumenthal - Norwalk, 1936; Parcel number 40. (Box 34)
      - Ella Louise Disbrow - Norwalk, 1938; Parcel number 32. (Box 34)
      - Ella Louise Disbrow - condemnation - Norwalk, 1937-1939 (Box 34)
      - Miller - Park - Fairfield, 1937; Parcel number 1. (Box 34)
      - Marguerite K. Mason - Fairfield, 1937; Parcel number 2. (Box 34)
      - Elinor T. Colie - Fairfield, 1937; Parcel number 3. (Box 34)
      - Julia M. W. Gault - Fairfield, 1936-1938; Parcel number 4. (Box 34)
      - Hattie A. Bulkley - Fairfield, 1936-1937; Parcel number 5. (Box 34)
      - Alvin D. Wadsworth - Fairfield, 1936-1937; Parcel number 6. (Box 34)
      - Alice M. G. Putney - Fairfield, 1936-1937; Parcel number 7. (Box 34)
      - Marion L. Giblin - Fairfield, 1937; Parcel number 9. (Box 34)
      - George Ferris - Fairfield, 1937; Parcel number 10. (Box 34)
      - Beatrice S. Binger - Fairfield, 1937; Parcel number 12. (Box 34)
      - Elizabeth Botsford - Fairfield, 1937; Parcel number 13. (Box 34)
      - Greenfield Land and Investment Co. - Fairfield, 1936-1937; Parcel number 14. (Box 34)
      - Elizabeth B. Brett - Fairfield, 1936; Parcel number 15. (Box 34)
      - Martin Hidu - Fairfield, 1937; Parcel number 18. (Box 34)
      - Eugene B. Burr - Fairfield, 1937; Parcel number 20. (Box 34)
      - Robert C. Flack - Fairfield, 1937; Parcel number 21. (Box 34)
      - Charles P. Andrews - Fairfield, 1937; Parcel number 29. (Box 34)
      - Kalman and Amelia Gubics - Fairfield, 1936-1937; Parcel number 43. (Box 34)
      - Bridgeport Hydraulic Company - Fairfield, 1937; Parcel number 44. (Box 34)
      - Charles S. Seeley - Fairfield, 1937; Parcel number 54. (Box 34)
      - Edward L. Cullen - Fairfield - Easton, 1936; Parcel number 55C. (Box 34)
      - Lila J. Seeley - Fairfield, 1936; 2 folders; Parcel number 56 and 56B. (Box 34)
      - Edward A. Skane - Fairfield, 1936; Parcel number 57. (Box 34)
      - Marie P. Phelps estate - Fairfield, 1938 (Box 34)
      - Jessie Banks, individually and in trust for Frank Lobdell - Fairfield, 1937-1938 (Box 34)
      - Heirs of Rufus B. Jennings - Fairfield, 1938-1939 (Box 34)
      - James B. Smith - Fairfield, 1938 (Box 34)
      - Margaret Carter Wilkinson - Fairfield, 1937 (Box 34)
      - William McCarthy - Westport, 1935-1936; Parcel number 1. (Box 34)
      - Justin Sturm - Westport, 1936; Parcel number 2. (Box 34)
      - Edward R. Pidgeon - Westport, 1936; Parcel number 3. (Box 34)
      - Lorenzo DiDomenica - Westport, 1937; Parcel number 4. (Box 34)
      - Alma E. Thomas - Westport, 1936; Parcel number 5. (Box 34)
      - Lillian Blount - Westport, 1937; Parcel number 6. (Box 34)
      - Ethel E. Quirion - Westport, 1936; Parcel number 6.5. (Box 34)
      - Louis Griss - Westport, 1936; Parcel number 7. (Box 34)
      - Louis A. Klingenberg - Westport, 1935-1936; Parcel number 8. (Box 34)
      - Clara Draves Burtsche, et al. - Westport, 1937; Parcel number 9. (Box 34)
      - Rachel M. Taylor - Westport, 1936; Parcel number 10. (Box 34)
      - Helen W. Smith - Westport, 1937; Parcel number 11. (Box 34)
      - Jason A. Barber - Westport, 1937; Parcel number 12. (Box 34)
      - Claire H. Mitchell - Westport, 1936; Parcel number 13. (Box 34)
      - Albert U. Langenegger - Westport, 1937; 2 folders; Parcel number 14. (Box 34)
      - Louise Cosslett - Westport, 1936-1937; Parcel number 15. (Box 34)
      - Castle West Corp. - Westport, 1936; Parcel number 16A and 16B. (Box 34)
      - Bonnie M. Stedman - Westport, 1936-1937; Parcel number 17. (Box 34)
      - Westport Estates Inc. - Westport, 1935-1939; Parcel number 18. (Box 34)
      - John B. Warnock - Westport, 1936-1937; Parcel number 19. (Box 34)
    - Betts, Insurance Commissioner v. Connecticut Life Insurance Co. of Waterbury, 1899 (Box 35)
    - Betts, Insurance Commissioner v. The Wooster Insurance Co. of Danbury, 1899 (Box 35)
    - Burr Estate, 1900-1902 (Box 35)
    - City of Hartford v. Maslen, et al., 1902-1903 (Box 35)
    - Cologne Re-Insurance Co. v. Charles S. Mersick, State Treasurer, 1900 (Box 35)
    - Graham's appeal from order - decree, 1902 (Box 35)
    - Hopkins, Mary Francis - Estate of, 1902 (Box 35)
    - Mersick, Treasurer, as Trustee vs. Hartford and West Hartford Horse Railroad Co., 1900 (Box 35)
    - Norton, et al. appeal from probate Gilman Estate, 1901 (Box 35)
    - State vs. Barber, 1902 (Box 35)
    - State vs. Bliss, et al., 1901 (Box 35)
    - State vs. Bushnell, et al., 1901 (Box 35)
    - State vs. Connorton, et al., 1899 (Box 35)
    - State vs. Cooke, 1900 (Box 35)
    - State vs. Cooley, 1898-1899 (Box 35)
    - State vs. Dickerman, et al., 1900 (Box 35)
    - State vs. Flint, et al., 1899 (Box 35)
    - State vs. Francis, et al., 1899 (Box 35)
    - State vs. Granger, et al., 1899 (Box 35)
    - State vs. Kellogg, 1900 (Box 35)
    - State vs. Lloyd, et al., 1899-1900 (Box 35)
    - State vs. Lord, 1900 (Box 35)
    - State vs. Maloy, et al., 1899-1900 (Box 35)
    - State vs. McKee, 1902 (Box 35)
    - State vs. Morehouse, et al., 1900 (Box 35)
    - State vs. Noble, et al., 1900 (Box 35)
    - State vs. Pratt, et al., 1901 (Box 35)
    - State vs. Ripley, et al., 1899 (Box 35)
    - State vs. Russell, et al., 1901 (Box 35)
    - State vs. Ryan, et al., 1900-1901 (Box 35)
    - State vs. Stent, et al., 1900 (Box 35)
    - State vs. Stewart, et al., 1901 (Box 35)
    - State vs. Travelers Insurance Co., 1899 (Box 35)
    - State vs. Ulrich, 1899 (Box 35)
    - State vs. Willett, 1902 (Box 35)
    - Almon E. Plumb vs. Percy L. Johnson, 1901 (Box 35)
    - American Steamship and Hotels Company and the Middlesex Banking Company - agreement, 1903 March (Box 35)
    - Banking, 1903-1905 (Box 35)
    - The Bridgeport Trust Company Administrator's Appeal from Probate - Reservation, 1904 December (Box 35)
    - Charles H. Nettleton appeal from Probate, 1903 (Box 35)
    - The City of Hartford and Board of Park Commissioners agreement with State of Connecticut concerning monument site, 1902 (Box 35)
      An agreement between the city of Hartford, Board of Park Commissioners, and First Connecticut Heavy Artillery Regimental Association "to erect a monument as a memorial of its services at a point on the Capitol grounds, at Hartford, to be designated by the comptroller..."
    - Columbia Trust Company restraining order, 1908-1909 (Box 35)
    - The Connecticut Savings Bank of New Haven vs. James F. Kelly, et al., 1901 (Box 35)
    - Connecticut State Firemen's Association - claim of Eugene M. Wilson, 1908 (Box 35)
    - Estate of Betsey Lawrence, undated (Box 35)
    - Estate of George T. Gilman, 1904-1905 (Box 35)
    - Ferris Estate, 1904 June 2 (Box 35)
    - George M. Baldwin vs. State of Connecticut, 1908 (Box 35)
    - Harriet F. Merwin vs. Percy L. Johnson, 1901 (Box 35)
    - In re blind, circa 1904 (Box 35)
    - In re estate of Joseph McClellan, 1906 (Box 35)
    - In re estate of Oakley S. Barker, 1905 (Box 35)
    - In re Fusco vs. Woodruff, 1904 (Box 35)
    - In re Jennie McClentic, circa 1905 (Box 35)
    - In re Meriden Electric Railroad Company bonds, circa 1904-1906 (Box 35)
    - In re Morgan School, circa 1904 (Box 35)
    - In re Omega Steel Company and the Middlesex Banking Company agreement, 1903 April 23 (Box 35)
    - John M. Murdoch, State Attorney vs. George E. Elliot, et al., 1900 March 3 (Box 35)
    - Malcolm Graham, Jr., executor, appeal from Probate, 1902 (Box 35)
    - Mansfield vs. State, et al., 1906 (Box 35)
    - Military hearing, 1907 November 18 (Box 35)
    - Minkwite vs. Spearfield, 1901 (Box 35)
    - Miscellaneous, circa 1883-1903, undated (Box 35)
      Folder consists of notes; court calendars; Final Report of the Commissioners for Grading the Capitol Grounds, January 1883; The Lawyers' Surety Company of New York statement; Proposed Uniform Bill relating to Fraternal Beneficiary Associations as prepared by the Committee on Fraternal Insurance of the National Convention of Insurance Commissioners, 1903; and Judicial Status of the Maccabee Orders in the Supreme Court of the State of Ohio, circa 1903.
    - Montville Street Railway Company to the Treasurer of the State of Connecticut - first mortgage, 1899-1900 (Box 35)
    - Option for purchasing armory site, 1902 August (Box 35)
    - Osborn case, 1904 (Box 35)
    - Peoples Savings Bank vs. Goodsell, 1901 (Box 35)
    - Petition of Clara Turcotte, 1901 (Box 35)
    - Power of Attorney for the Fidelity and Deposit Company of Maryland, 1899-1903 (Box 35)
    - Reasons of appeal in-re Gallup, Treasurer, circa 1901 (Box 35)
    - Release of mortgage Charles S. Mersick, Treasurer of the State of Connecticut to the Aetna Life Insurance Company, 1899 February 20 (Box 35)
    - School Fund Department legal expenses, 1903-1904 (Box 35)
    - State vs. F.C. Allen, 1898 May 7 (Box 35)
    - State vs. Mix, et al., 1909 (Box 35)
    - State vs. Suffield and Thompsonville Bridge Company, circa 1908-1910 (Box 35)
    - State of Connecticut vs. Arthur H. Merrill, et al., 1905 (Box 35)
    - State of Connecticut vs. Ellen F. Sherman, 1905-1912 (Box 35)
    - State of Connecticut vs. Francis L. Knapp, et al., 1905-1906 (Box 36)
    - The State of Connecticut vs. H. Frank Beck, et al., 1913-1914 (Box 36)
    - State of Connecticut vs. Henriette E. Wynne, et al., 1906 (Box 36)
    - State of Connecticut vs. Joseph J. Fernand, et al., 1912-1914 (Box 36)
    - State of Connecticut vs. Joseph Holcomb, et al., 1905 (Box 36)
    - State of Connecticut vs. Mutual Life Insurance Company of New York, 1905 (Box 36)
    - State of Connecticut vs. The Equitable Life Assurance Society of the United States, 1905 (Box 36)
    - Upson vs. Johnson, 1901 (Box 36)
    - Vibbart vs. State, et al., circa 1906 (Box 36)
    - Vermilye, William Gerard, 1900 (Box 36)
    - Andrea Salamarco vs. Peoples Saving Bank, 1917 (Box 37)
    - Charles F. Kent, et al. vs. George E. Hinman, et al., 1917-1918 (Box 37)
    - Charles R. Burt Trust, 1914-1921 (Box 37)
    - Claim of Hattie and Harry Dunning, 1923 (Box 37)
    - Davis compensation case (Tuberculosis Commission), 1917 (Box 37)
    - Ely vs. Highway Commissioner, 1918 (Box 37)
    - Estate of Margaretha Reinecke, 1917 (Box 37)
    - Estelle W. Douglas vs. Charles J. Bennett, Highway Commissioner, 1915-1917 (Box 37)
    - French Cable Company, 1915 (Box 37)
    - George A. Parker, et al. vs. State Park Commissioners vs. Lillian Newkirk, et al., 1917-1918 (Box 37)
    - Gilpatric papers, circa 1919-1926 (Box 37)
    - Harrie T. Hoyt vs. Laura May Bliss, et al., 1918-1919 (Box 37)
    - Irving Smith vs. Bennett, Highway Commissioner, 1918 (Box 37)
    - Joseph J. Fields vs. Charles J. Bennett, Highway Commissioner, 1916-1917 (Box 37)
    - Lane, et al. vs. Whitaker, et al., 1921-1922 (Box 37)
    - Louis A. Jacobs vs. Charles J. Bennett, Highway Commissioner, 1916 (Box 37)
    - Modeste and Whitby vs. Public Utilities Commission, 1921-1922 (Box 37)
    - Savin Rock Park Commission, circa 1918-1921 (Box 37)
    - Smedley Company vs. Charles J. Bennett, Highway Commissioner, 1917-1918 (Box 37)
    - State vs. Henry Boylan, 1917 (Box 37)
    - State vs. Meriden, Middletown, and Guilford Electric Railway Company, 1914-1918 (Box 37)
    - State of Connecticut vs. Danial A. Markham, et al., 1922 (Box 37)
    - State of Connecticut vs. Home Trust Company, 1908-1917 (Box 37)
    - Thomas M. Wilson vs. Charles J. Bennett, Highway Commissioner, 1916 (Box 37)
    - William H. Corbin, Tax Commissioner vs. Henry H. Townshend, Administrator C.T.A., 1918 (Box 37)
    - Wolfe vs. Bennett, Highway Commissioner, 1917-1918 (Box 37)
    - American Real Estate Company, 1911-1921; 4 folders (Box 38)
    - Berwind-White Coal Mining Company in re corporation tax, 1916 (Box 38)
    - Board of Control agreement in re Connecticut School for Imbiciles - sewage disposal, 1915-1916 (Box 38)
    - Claim of State vs. Melia Tiezzi, 1915-1916 (Box 38)
    - Claims heard, 1917 (Box 38)
    - Connecticut River Bridge and Highway Districts appeal, 1916 (Box 38)
    - Darrell estate, in re inheritance tax, 1916 (Box 38)
    - DeAngelis, Antonio, 1918 (Box 38)
    - Emma R. Skinner vs. Connecticut School for Imbiciles, 1914-1916 (Box 38)
    - Estate of Alfred A. Pope, 1912-1917; 2 folders (Box 38)
    - Estate of Henry C. Judd, 1917 (Box 38)
    - Estate of James J. Goodwin appeal from Probate of William H. Corbin, Tax Commissioner of the State of Connecticut, 1917 (Box 38)
    - Estate of Mary A. Smith, Windham, Connecticut, 1902 September 8 (Box 38)
    - Estate of Matsie J. Shipman, 1917 (Box 38)
    - Estate of Sarah H. Nye, 1915 (Box 38)
    - George H. Warner's appeal from Probate, 1916-1917 (Box 38)
    - Hartford Life Insurance Company application to State Treasurer, 1915-1916 (Box 38)
    - Hartford Poster Advertising Company vs. Charles D. Burns, Secretary of the State, et al., 1916 (Box 38)
    - In re Aetna Indemnity Company, 1911-1912 (Box 38)
    - In re application of Edward Brush Sons, Inc., 1916-1917 (Box 38)
    - In re application of G. Fox & Company and James H. Bennett, their manager, for registration, 1916 (Box 38)
    - In re School Fund mortgage, 1899 (Box 38)
    - In the matter of the application of John T. Sloan, administrator of the estate of Henrietta Hooker, deceased, 1902 (Box 38)
    - J. Jaffred Butler, temporary administrator, et al. vs. Rose Harriet Richardson, et al., 1899 (Box 38)
    - James D. McKenna, et al. vs. Frank S. Butterworth, et al., 1921-1922 (Box 38)
    - John M. Murdoch, et al. vs. George E. Elliott, et al., 1898 (Box 38)
    - Ketchum, Guernsey, 1899 (Box 38)
    - Life Publishing Co. vs. Branchville Fresh Air Association, 1916 (Box 38)
    - Miscellaneous, circa 1899-1900, undated (Box 38)
      Folder contains a blank application form for commitment to an institution for the insane; shell fish special acts; a booklet on "Facts Regarding the Invention of the Voting Machine"; and a blank application for bond by Fidelity and Deposit Company of Maryland.
    - Mosquito elimination claims, 1916-1917 (Box 38)
    - New Britain Gas Light Company appeal from order of Utilities Commission, 1916-1919 (Box 38)
    - Plainfield fire damages cases, 1914-1917 (Box 38)
    - Putnam Savings Bank restraining order, revocation of, 1916 (Box 38)
    - Report on appraisal condition of Hartford Life Insurance Company, 1900 (Box 38)
    - Richardson vs. Bennett, Highway Commissioner, 1916-1917 (Box 38)
    - Ryan vs. Tuberculosis Comission, 1916 (Box 38)
    - Sage Allen & Co. vs. Curtiss P. Gladding, et al. Pharmacy Commission, 1916 (Box 38)
    - Sarah J. Morehouse et al. appeal from Public Utilities Commission, 1916 (Box 38)
    - Shellfish Board of Relief, 1916 (Box 38)
    - State vs. Aetna Indemnity Company, 1911-1916 (Box 38)
    - State vs. Bristol and Plainville Tramway Company, 1916 (Box 38)
    - State vs. Fountain Water Co., 1915-1916 (Box 38)
    - State of Connecticut vs. The Mad River Co., 1916-1917 (Box 38)
    - State vs. Phoenix Mutual Life Insurance Company, 1916 (Box 38)
    - State vs. Shawnee Fire Insurance Company, 1911-1916 (Box 38)
    - State vs. United Electric Light and Water Company, 1913-1916 (Box 38)
    - State vs. William H. Gibney, 1916 (Box 38)
    - State of Connecticut vs. Anna M. Palmer, et al., 1906-1916 (Box 38)
    - United Illuminating Company appeal and complaint from Public Utilities Commission, 1914 (Box 38)
    - Washington Bridge maintenance of by Connecticut Company, 1916 (Box 38)
    - Windsor Water Company, 1916 (Box 38)
- Series 3. Subject Files, bulk
  - T002854, 0.5 cubic feet
    - Attorney General, Office of - organization - case list, circa 1929 (Box 5)
    - Branford Harbor - federal legislation, 1929 (Box 5)
    - Bridgeport Trust Company and Bridgeport City Bank consolidation, 1929 (Box 5)
    - Civil service - Postmaster, U.S. - ineligiability, 1927 (Box 5)
    - Correspondence - Attorney General, 1929-1930 (Box 5)
    - Connecticut National Guard - Ernest Averill - corespondence, 1928-1930 (Box 5)
    - Correspondence, official - Averill, Ernest, 1927-1930 (Box 5)
    - Correspondence, personal - Averill, Ernest, 1927-1931 (Box 5)
    - Correspondence - Avery, C. L., 1931 (Box 5)
    - Expenses - receipts - Ernest A. Averill, 1927-1930 (Box 5)
    - Fraternal organizations - membership - Ernest L. Averill, 1922-1929 (Box 5)
    - News clippings - various topics, 1927-1930 (Box 5)
    - State Foresters of New England, circa 1929 (Box 5)
    - Taxes - inheritance, Federal - American Taxpayers League, 1928 (Box 5)
    - Taxes - inheritance, Federal - correspondence, 1925-1926 (Box 5)
    - Taxes - inheritance, Federal - court cases, 1925 (Box 5)